explorerforum.com 2017-12-22

# Serious Explorations' Privacy Policy

August 14, 2016

At Serious Explorations we recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal   
information we receive and collect when you use Serious Explorations's services, as well as some of the steps we   
take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing your personal   
information with us.

* Serious Explorations collects personal information when you register on the ExplorerForum.com message board.

* Serious Explorations uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about   
how you use the Serious Explorations websites in order to improve the quality of our services.

* Serious Explorations's servers automatically record information when you visit our website including the URL,   
IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. This is typical of all web servers.

Uses

* We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display   
customized content and advertising.

* We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve Serious   
Explorations technologies and services.

* We may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties outside of Serious Explorations.

* We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal   
process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services.

* Serious Explorations processes personal information on our server in the United States of America. In some   
cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country.

Your choices

* We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. You can find more   
information about your choices in the privacy notices or FAQs for specific services.

* You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of   
our features or services may not function properly as a result.

* We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you   
correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. 

* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Serious Explorations users based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. 

* You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content [network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

* Serious Explorations has been equipped with an affiliate program called Skimlinks.  
If you click an affiliated link on our website and buy anything from the associated site, Serious Explorations will directly benefit.  
Unlike other affiliate programs, Skimlinks is automatic. Any link on this website that is associated with them will be automatically converted to an affiliate link.  
Visit
